NEIL ORIBELLO

• DETAILS •

14981 95a Ave Surrey, V3R 7T6 Canada 7782236406 neil.oribello@gmail.com

• LINKS •

neoribello.github.io/portfolio/

• SKILLS •

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

SCSS

PostCSS

LESS

Bootstrap

React

Vue

Gatsby

Git

JSON

JIRA

Trello

PROFILE

Enthusiastic Front End Developer with 1+ years of experience designing and building websites in the Real Estate industry. Proficient with HTML, CSS(SASS and POSTCSS), JavaScript and JS Frameworks (React.js and Vue.js), with knowledge of User Interface and Experience Design.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Web Designer at Real Estate Webmasters, Vancouver

March 2019 — March 2020

- Web Designer at Real Estate Webmasters a web technology provider for the top 1% of real estate professionals in North America.
- Translates mock ups into front end components. The languages that were mainly used in my tenure: HTML, SASS, POSTCSS, JavaScript, Vue.js
- Designs web layouts for the clients using the Adobe Creative Cloud.
- Communicates with clients directly with regard to design, preferences, changes and deadlines.
- Collaborates with internal teams.e.g. quality, sales, other developer, designer and project manager for the completion of projects
- Consistently meets deadlines and positive feedback from customers and team members

Web Developer Intern at Cucumber Marketing, Vancouver

August 2017 — October 2017

· Student Intern - Redesigning web pages through WordPress

EDUCATION

Digital Design and Development Diploma, British Columbia Institute of Technology, Vancouver

September 2018 — June 2019

- · Graduated with distinction in my class
- GPA above 3.5

New Media Design and Web Development Certificate, British Columbia Institute of Technology, Vancouver

September 2016 — September 2017

- · Graduated with distinction in my class
- GPA above 3.5

★ PROJECTS

Personal Portfolio

- · Developed a personal project on Gatsby and Strapi
- Implemented a headless CMS (Strapi) where I consume API using GraphQL
- Primarily developed front-end components, while connected to a Strapi backend
- Developed using an Agile approach by myself, using 2-week sprints and Trello

Shopify Ecommerce Project

- Quarantine project where I started learning Shopify
- Built based on React where I picked a inspiration site to base styles off
- Supports REST API functionality
- Parses DATA from an API to display information of each product

Cart function project

- Cart function where items can be added, deleted or totaled.
- Shows a C.R.U.D system

REFERENCES

References available upon request